[
  {
    "name": "Commonly used verbs",
    "slug": "commonly-used-verbs",
    "tags": ["#german", "#verbs"],
    "cards": [
      { "front": "langern", "back": "To extend" },
      { "front": "wollen", "back": "To want" },
      { "front": "gehen", "back": "To go" },
      { "front": "tragen", "back": "To carry" },
      { "front": "sehen", "back": "To see" },
      { "front": "fragen", "back": "To ask" },
      { "front": "machen", "back": "To do/make" },
      { "front": "schreiben", "back": "To write" },
      { "front": "beobacheten", "back": "To observe" },
      { "front": "uberlegen", "back": "To consider" },
      { "front": "lesen", "back": "To read" },
      { "front": "rauchen", "back": "To smoke" },
      { "front": "benutzen", "back": "To use" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "German Conjunctions",
    "slug": "conjunktionen",
    "tags": ["#german", "#grammar", "#conjunctions"],
    "cards": [
      { "front": "und", "back": "And" },
      { "front": "aber", "back": "but" },
      { "front": "denn", "back": "because" },
      { "front": "oder", "back": "or" },
      { "front": "sondern", "back": "but (as in but rather)" },
      { "front": "beziehungsweise", "back": "or, or more precisely" },
      { "front": "doch", "back": "but, however" },
      { "front": "jedoch", "back": "but, however" },
      { "front": "allein", "back": "(rare expression) but unfortunately" },
      { "front": "entweder … oder", "back": "either … or" },
      { "front": "sowohl … als auch", "back": "both … and" },
      { "front": "weder … noch", "back": "neither … nor" },
      {
        "front": "einerseits, … andererseits",
        "back": "on the one hand … on the other hand"
      },
      { "front": "mal … mal", "back": "sometimes … sometimes" },
      { "front": "teils … teils", "back": "partly … partly" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "German Subordinating Conjunctions",
    "slug": "conjunktionen-2",
    "tags": ["#german", "#grammar", "#subordinating", "#conjunctions"],
    "cards": [
      { "front": "bevor", "back": "before" },
      { "front": "nachdem", "back": "after" },
      { "front": "ehe", "back": "before" },
      {
        "front": "seit, seitdem",
        "back": "since (indicating time, not a causality)"
      },
      { "front": "während", "back": "while, during, whereas" },
      { "front": "als", "back": "when (in describing past events)" },
      {
        "front": "wenn",
        "back": "when (describing present and future), if, whenever"
      },
      { "front": "wann", "back": "when (for questions only)" },
      { "front": "bis", "back": "until, by" },
      { "front": "obwohl", "back": "although" },
      { "front": "als ob, als wenn, als", "back": "as if" },
      { "front": "sooft", "back": "as often as (whenever)" },
      { "front": "sobald", "back": "as soon as" },
      { "front": "solange", "back": "as long as" },
      { "front": "da", "back": "because" },
      { "front": "indem", "back": "by … -ing" },
      { "front": "weil", "back": "because" },
      {
        "front": "ob",
        "back": "whether*, if (*only use when you could say “whether” in English as well)"
      },
      { "front": "falls", "back": "in case, if" },
      { "front": "wenn", "back": "if, when" },
      { "front": "um … zu", "back": "in order to" },
      { "front": "dass", "back": "that" },
      { "front": "sodass", "back": "so that" },
      { "front": "damit", "back": "so that" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Everyday expressions",
    "slug": "everyday-expressions",
    "tags": ["#german", "#expressions", "#popularwords"],
    "cards": []
  },
  {
    "name": "A Dictionary Deck 1",
    "slug": "dictionary-deck-1",
    "tags": ["#german"],
    "cards": [
      { "front": "abbiegen", "back": "turn" },
      { "front": "Abend", "back": "evening" },
      { "front": "Abendessen", "back": "dinner" },
      { "front": "Abendkleidung", "back": "evening dress" },
      { "front": "Abenteuer", "back": "adventure" },
      { "front": "aber", "back": "but" },
      { "front": "abfahren", "back": "leave (irr.)" },
      { "front": "Abfall", "back": "waste" },
      { "front": "abfliegen", "back": "start" },
      { "front": "Abgabe", "back": "tax" },
      { "front": "abgehoben", "back": "withdrawn" },
      { "front": "abgenutzt", "back": "worn-out" },
      { "front": "Abgeordneter", "back": "representative" },
      { "front": "Abgrenzung", "back": "boundary" },
      { "front": "Abhang", "back": "slope" },
      { "front": "abhängen", "back": "depend" },
      { "front": "abhängig", "back": "dependent" },
      { "front": "Abhängigkeit", "back": "dependence" },
      { "front": "Abhängig sein von", "back": "depend on" },
      { "front": "abhärten", "back": "harden" },
      { "front": "abheben (Geld)", "back": "withdraw (irr.)" },
      { "front": "abklären", "back": "clear" },
      { "front": "abkühlen", "back": "cool" },
      { "front": "ablehnen", "back": "refuse" },
      { "front": "Ablehnung", "back": "refusal" },
      { "front": "Abmachung", "back": "arrangement" },
      { "front": "Abnahme", "back": "lessening" },
      { "front": "abnehmen", "back": "decrease" },
      { "front": "abnehmen (Hut)", "back": "take off" },
      { "front": "abnutzen", "back": "wear down" },
      { "front": "Abnutzung", "back": "wear" },
      { "front": "Abrechnung", "back": "account" },
      { "front": "Abreise", "back": "departure" },
      { "front": "abreisen", "back": "start" },
      { "front": "abreisen nach", "back": "leave for" },
      { "front": "Absatz", "back": "heel" },
      { "front": "abschreiben", "back": "copy" },
      { "front": "Abschrift", "back": "copy" },
      { "front": "abseits vom Wege", "back": "out of the way" },
      { "front": "Absender", "back": "sender" },
      { "front": "Absicht", "back": "purpose" },
      { "front": "absichtlich", "back": "on purpose" },
      { "front": "absperren", "back": "lock" },
      { "front": "abstammen von", "back": "descend from" },
      { "front": "abstauben", "back": "dust" },
      { "front": "abstimmen", "back": "vote" },
      { "front": "Abstimmung", "back": "vote" },
      { "front": "Absturz", "back": "crash" },
      { "front": "abstürzen", "back": "crash" },
      { "front": "Abteilung", "back": "department" },
      { "front": "abwärts", "back": "downwards" },
      { "front": "Abwechslung", "back": "variety" },
      { "front": "abwesend", "back": "absent" },
      { "front": "Abwesenheit", "back": "absence" },
      { "front": "abzäunen", "back": "fence off" },
      { "front": "Abzug", "back": "print" },
      { "front": "acht", "back": "eight" },
      { "front": "achte", "back": "eighth" },
      { "front": "achtgeben (auf)", "back": "take care (of)" },
      { "front": "achtzehn", "back": "eighteen" },
      { "front": "achtzehnte", "back": "eighteenth" },
      { "front": "achtzig", "back": "eighty" },
      { "front": "achtzigste", "back": "eightieth" },
      { "front": "Adel", "back": "nobility" },
      { "front": "adeliger Herr", "back": "Lord" },
      { "front": "adoptieren", "back": "adopt" },
      { "front": "Adoption", "back": "adoption" },
      { "front": "Adresse", "back": "address" },
      { "front": "Affe", "back": "monkey" },
      { "front": "Afrika", "back": "Africa" },
      { "front": "Afrikaner", "back": "African" },
      { "front": "afrikanisch", "back": "African" },
      { "front": "Agent", "back": "agent" },
      { "front": "Agentur", "back": "agency" },
      { "front": "ähnlich", "back": "similar" },
      { "front": "Akt", "back": "act" },
      { "front": "Aktie", "back": "share" },
      { "front": "aktiv", "back": "active" },
      { "front": "Aktivität", "back": "activity" },
      { "front": "Alarm", "back": "alarm" },
      { "front": "Alkohol", "back": "alcohol" },
      { "front": "alkoholfreie Getränke", "back": "soft drinks" },
      { "front": "all", "back": "all" },
      { "front": "alle Leute", "back": "all men" },
      {
        "front": "alle Menschen sind gleichwertig",
        "back": "all men are equal"
      },
      { "front": "alle paar Stunden", "back": "every few hours" },
      {
        "front": "alle Völker der Welt",
        "back": "all the peoples of the world"
      },
      {
        "front": "alle Völker der Erde",
        "back": "all the peoples of the earth"
      },
      { "front": "Allee", "back": "avenue" },
      { "front": "allein", "back": "alone" },
      { "front": "alles", "back": "everything" },
      { "front": "alles beliebige", "back": "anything" },
      { "front": "allgemein", "back": "general" },
      { "front": "Allgemeinheit", "back": "community" },
      { "front": "allmählich", "back": "gradual" },
      { "front": "als", "back": "as" },
      { "front": "als (bei Steigerung)", "back": "than" },
      { "front": "als (zu der Zeit)", "back": "when" },
      { "front": "als ob", "back": "as though" },
      { "front": "alt", "back": "old" },
      { "front": "alte Bücher", "back": "old books" },
      { "front": "Alter", "back": "age" },
      { "front": "älter", "back": "older" },
      { "front": "ältere", "back": "elder" },
      { "front": "älteste", "back": "oldest" },
      { "front": "altmodisch", "back": "old-fashioned" },
      { "front": "am besten", "back": "best" },
      { "front": "am Boden von", "back": "at the bottom of" },
      { "front": "am Ende des Stücks", "back": "at the close of the play" },
      { "front": "am Körper tragen", "back": "wear (irr.)" },
      { "front": "am Leben", "back": "alive" },
      { "front": "am Leben sein", "back": "be alive" },
      { "front": "am meisten", "back": "most" },
      { "front": "am schlechtesten", "back": "worst" },
      { "front": "am schlimmsten", "back": "worst" },
      { "front": "am weitesten", "back": "farthest" },
      { "front": "am wenigsten", "back": "least" },
      { "front": "Amerika", "back": "America" },
      { "front": "amerikanisch", "back": "American" },
      { "front": "Amt", "back": "office" },
      { "front": "amtlich", "back": "official" },
      { "front": "amüsier dich", "back": "amuse yourself" },
      { "front": "amüsieren", "back": "amuse" },
      { "front": "an", "back": "at" },
      { "front": "an Bord", "back": "aboard" },
      { "front": "an Deck", "back": "on board" },
      { "front": "an der Spitze von", "back": "at the head of" },
      { "front": "an der Wand", "back": "on the wall" },
      { "front": "an die Kälte gewöhnt", "back": "accustomed to the cold" },
      {
        "front": "an einer Konferenz teilnehmen",
        "back": "attend a conference"
      },
      { "front": "an jedem Tag", "back": "everyday" },
      { "front": "an seiner Seite", "back": "at his side" },
      { "front": "anbauen", "back": "grow (irr.)" },
      { "front": "anbieten", "back": "offer" },
      { "front": "Anblick", "back": "sight" },
      { "front": "andauernd", "back": "permanently" },
      { "front": "anderenfalls", "back": "otherwise" },
      { "front": "anderer", "back": "other" },
      { "front": "Änderung", "back": "change" },
      { "front": "anerkennen", "back": "appreciate" },
      { "front": "Anerkennung", "back": "recognition" },
      { "front": "Anfang", "back": "start" },
      { "front": "anfangen", "back": "start" },
      { "front": "anfeuchten", "back": "damp" },
      { "front": "angebaut", "back": "grown" },
      { "front": "angeben", "back": "declare" },
      { "front": "Angebot", "back": "offer" },
      { "front": "angehäuft", "back": "piled up" },
      { "front": "Angelegenheit", "back": "matter" },
      { "front": "angelehnt", "back": "leant" },
      { "front": "angeliefert", "back": "delivered" },
      { "front": "Angelrute", "back": "fishing-rod" },
      { "front": "angenehm", "back": "pleasant" },
      { "front": "Angewohnheit", "back": "habit" },
      { "front": "angezogen", "back": "dressed" },
      { "front": "angezündet", "back": "lit" },
      { "front": "angreifen", "back": "attack" },
      { "front": "Angriff", "back": "attack" },
      { "front": "Angst", "back": "fear" },
      { "front": "Angst haben vor", "back": "be afraid of" },
      { "front": "anhalten", "back": "stop" },
      { "front": "Anhänger", "back": "follower" },
      { "front": "anhäufen", "back": "heap" },
      { "front": "anklagen", "back": "charge" },
      { "front": "ankommen", "back": "arrive" },
      { "front": "Ankunft", "back": "arrival" },
      { "front": "Anlass", "back": "occasion" },
      { "front": "anlehnen", "back": "lean (irr.)" },
      { "front": "anliefern", "back": "deliver" },
      { "front": "Anlieferung", "back": "delivery" },
      { "front": "anlocken", "back": "attract" },
      { "front": "anmalen", "back": "paint" },
      { "front": "Anmerkung", "back": "note" },
      { "front": "annehmen", "back": "accept" },
      { "front": "Annehmlichkeit", "back": "convenience" },
      { "front": "annoncieren", "back": "advertise" },
      { "front": "anordnen", "back": "order" },
      { "front": "Anordnung", "back": "order" },
      { "front": "anprobieren", "back": "try on" },
      { "front": "Anrecht", "back": "right" },
      { "front": "Anreiz", "back": "attraction" },
      { "front": "Anruf (Telefon)", "back": "telephone call" },
      { "front": "anrufen", "back": "telephone" },
      { "front": "anrufen (Telefon)", "back": "call" },
      { "front": "anschieben", "back": "push" },
      { "front": "Anschlagtafel", "back": "notice board" },
      { "front": "Anschluss", "back": "connection" },
      { "front": "ansehen (verb)", "back": "look at" },
      { "front": "Ansiedlung", "back": "settlement" },
      { "front": "Anspruch", "back": "pretence" },
      { "front": "ansteigen", "back": "rise (irr.)" },
      { "front": "anstellen", "back": "employ" },
      { "front": "Anstellung", "back": "engagement" },
      { "front": "Anstoß", "back": "push" },
      { "front": "Anstrengung", "back": "effort" },
      { "front": "Anstrich", "back": "paint" },
      { "front": "Anteil", "back": "share" },
      { "front": "antik", "back": "ancient" },
      { "front": "Antriebsfeder", "back": "spring" },
      { "front": "Antwort", "back": "reply" },
      { "front": "antworten", "back": "reply" },
      { "front": "anvertrauen", "back": "entrust" },
      { "front": "Anweisungen", "back": "directions" },
      { "front": "anwenden", "back": "apply" },
      { "front": "anwesend", "back": "present" },
      { "front": "Anwesenheit", "back": "presence" },
      { "front": "anziehen", "back": "attract" },
      { "front": "anziehen (Person)", "back": "dress" },
      { "front": "Anzug", "back": "suit" },
      { "front": "anzünden", "back": "light (irr.)" },
      { "front": "Apfel", "back": "apple" },
      { "front": "Apotheker", "back": "chemist" },
      { "front": "Appetit", "back": "appetite" },
      { "front": "applaudieren", "back": "applaud" },
      { "front": "Applaus", "back": "applause" },
      { "front": "April", "back": "April" },
      { "front": "Arbeit", "back": "work" },
      { "front": "Arbeit (Anstrengung)", "back": "labour" },
      { "front": "arbeiten", "back": "work" },
      { "front": "Arbeiter(in)", "back": "worker" },
      { "front": "Arbeiterklasse", "back": "working-class" },
      { "front": "Arbeitgeber", "back": "employer" },
      { "front": "Arbeitnehmer", "back": "employee" },
      { "front": "arbeitslos", "back": "unemployed" },
      { "front": "Arbeitslosigkeit", "back": "unemployment" },
      { "front": "Arbeitstag", "back": "working-day" },
      { "front": "Arbeitsvermittlung", "back": "labour exchange" },
      { "front": "ärgerlich", "back": "annoying" },
      { "front": "Ärgernis", "back": "nuisance" },
      { "front": "Argument", "back": "argument" },
      { "front": "Argwohn", "back": "suspicion" },
      { "front": "Arm", "back": "arm" },
      { "front": "arm", "back": "poor" },
      { "front": "Armbanduhr", "back": "wristwatch" },
      { "front": "Ärmel", "back": "sleeve" },
      { "front": "Armut", "back": "poverty" },
      { "front": "Aroma", "back": "flavour" },
      { "front": "Arrest", "back": "arrest" },
      { "front": "Art", "back": "kind" },
      { "front": "Art und Weise", "back": "manner" },
      { "front": "Artigkeit", "back": "prettiness" },
      { "front": "Artikel", "back": "article" },
      { "front": "artistisch", "back": "artistic" },
      { "front": "Arzneimittel", "back": "drug" },
      { "front": "Arzt", "back": "physician" },
      { "front": "aß", "back": "ate" },
      { "front": "Asche", "back": "ashes" },
      { "front": "Asien", "back": "Asia" },
      { "front": "Assistent", "back": "assistant" },
      { "front": "Atem", "back": "breath" },
      { "front": "atmen", "back": "breathe" },
      { "front": "Atmen", "back": "breathing" },
      { "front": "atmend", "back": "breathing" },
      { "front": "attractiv", "back": "attractive" },
      { "front": "Attraktion", "back": "attraction" },
      { "front": "auch", "back": "too (nachgestellt)" },
      { "front": "auch nicht", "back": "nor" },
      { "front": "auf", "back": "up" },
      { "front": "auf (prep.)", "back": "upon" },
      { "front": "auf beiden Seiten", "back": "on either side" },
      {
        "front": "auf das Wohl der Braut trinken",
        "back": "drink to the health of the bride"
      },
      { "front": "auf dem Luftweg", "back": "by air" },
      { "front": "auf der Suche", "back": "searching" },
      {
        "front": "auf die eine oder andere Weise",
        "back": "in some way or other"
      },
      { "front": "auf ehrliche Weise", "back": "honestly" },
      { "front": "auf eigenartige Weise", "back": "peculiarly" },
      { "front": "auf einen Besuch hereinkommen", "back": "drop in" },
      { "front": "auf etwas deuten", "back": "point at something" },
      { "front": "auf feine Art", "back": "finely" },
      { "front": "auf Flaschen füllen", "back": "bottle" },
      { "front": "auf gierige Weise", "back": "greedily" },
      { "front": "auf grausame Weise", "back": "cruelly" },
      { "front": "auf höfliche Weise", "back": "politely" },
      { "front": "auf leichte Weise", "back": "easily" },
      { "front": "auf mechanische Weise", "back": "mechanically" },
      { "front": "auf mehr Arbeit begierig", "back": "eager for more work" },
      { "front": "auf meine Kosten", "back": "at my expense" },
      { "front": "auf natürliche Weise", "back": "naturally" },
      { "front": "auf nette Weise", "back": "nicely" },
      { "front": "auf Probe", "back": "on trial" },
      { "front": "auf schöne Weise", "back": "beautifully" },
      { "front": "auf schreckliche Art und Weise", "back": "terribly" },
      { "front": "auf tapfere Weise", "back": "bravely" },
      { "front": "auf Tour gehen", "back": "go on tour" },
      { "front": "auf trockene Art und Weise", "back": "dryly" },
      { "front": "auf und ab rennen", "back": "run up and down" },
      { "front": "Auf Wiedersehen !", "back": "goodbye !" },
      { "front": "auf wunderbare Art und Weise", "back": "wonderfully" },
      { "front": "auf zarte Weise", "back": "delicately" },
      { "front": "Aufbau", "back": "structure" },
      { "front": "aufbrauchen", "back": "use up" },
      { "front": "aufbrechen", "back": "start" },
      { "front": "Aufenthalt", "back": "stay" },
      { "front": "aufführen", "back": "perform" },
      { "front": "auffüllen", "back": "fill up" },
      { "front": "Aufgabe (gestellte)", "back": "task" },
      { "front": "aufgegangen", "back": "risen" },
      { "front": "aufgehen (Sonne etc)", "back": "rise (irr.)" },
      { "front": "aufgestanden", "back": "risen" },
      { "front": "aufgewacht", "back": "woken" },
      { "front": "aufgeweckt", "back": "woken" },
      { "front": "aufhalten", "back": "check" },
      { "front": "aufhäufen", "back": "pile up" },
      { "front": "aufheben", "back": "lift" },
      { "front": "aufhören", "back": "stop" },
      { "front": "aufknöpfen", "back": "unbutton" },
      { "front": "aufleuchten", "back": "flash" },
      { "front": "auflösen", "back": "dissolve" },
      { "front": "Aufmerksamkeit", "back": "attention" },
      { "front": "aufmuntern", "back": "cheer" },
      { "front": "aufpassen (auf)", "back": "pay attention (to)" },
      { "front": "aufrecht", "back": "upright" },
      { "front": "aufrechterhalten", "back": "maintain" },
      { "front": "aufregen", "back": "excite" },
      { "front": "aufregend", "back": "exciting" },
      { "front": "Aufregung", "back": "excitement" },
      { "front": "aufrichten", "back": "raise" },
      { "front": "aufrichtig", "back": "truly" },
      { "front": "aufrühren", "back": "stir up" },
      { "front": "aufs Neue", "back": "anew" },
      { "front": "Aufschrei", "back": "outcry" },
      { "front": "aufschreien", "back": "cry out" },
      { "front": "Aufstand", "back": "rising" },
      { "front": "aufstehen", "back": "stand up" },
      { "front": "aufsteigend", "back": "rising" },
      { "front": "aufstreichen", "back": "spread (irr.)" },
      { "front": "aufteilen", "back": "split (irr.)" },
      { "front": "Auftrag", "back": "order" },
      { "front": "aufwachen", "back": "wake (irr.)" },
      { "front": "aufwachsen", "back": "grow up" },
      { "front": "aufwärts", "back": "upwards" },
      { "front": "aufwecken", "back": "wake (irr.)" },
      { "front": "aufzeichnen", "back": "record" },
      { "front": "Aufzug(Br.)", "back": "lift" },
      { "front": "Aufzug(US)", "back": "elevator" },
      { "front": "Augapfel", "back": "eye-ball" },
      { "front": "Auge", "back": "eye" },
      { "front": "Augenblick", "back": "moment" },
      { "front": "Augenbraue", "back": "eyebrow" },
      { "front": "August", "back": "August" },
      { "front": "aus", "back": "out" },
      { "front": "aus (heraus)", "back": "out of" },
      { "front": "aus dem Gedächtnis", "back": "from memory" },
      { "front": "aus Erfahrung lernen", "back": "learn by experience" },
      { "front": "aus Erfahrung sprechen", "back": "speak from experience" },
      { "front": "aus Furcht", "back": "for fear" },
      { "front": "aus Furcht daß", "back": "for fear that" },
      { "front": "aus verschiedenen Gründen", "back": "for various reasons" },
      { "front": "aus zweiter Hand", "back": "second-hand" },
      { "front": "ausbessern", "back": "mend" },
      { "front": "ausbilden", "back": "train" },
      { "front": "Ausbildung", "back": "training" },
      { "front": "ausbreiten", "back": "spread (irr.)" },
      { "front": "Ausbruch", "back": "outbreak" },
      { "front": "ausdehnen", "back": "extend" },
      { "front": "Ausdehnung", "back": "extension" },
      { "front": "Ausdruck", "back": "print" },
      { "front": "ausdrücken", "back": "express" },
      { "front": "auseinander reißen", "back": "tear apart" },
      { "front": "Außenbezirke", "back": "outskirts" },
      { "front": "Außenseite", "back": "outside" },
      { "front": "außer", "back": "except" },
      { "front": "außer Dienst", "back": "off duty" },
      {
        "front": "außer du tust es selbst",
        "back": "except by doing it yourself"
      },
      {
        "front": "außer ein paar Fehlern",
        "back": "except for a few mistakes"
      },
      { "front": "außerdem", "back": "moreover" },
      { "front": "äußerer", "back": "outer" },
      { "front": "außergewöhnlich", "back": "extraordinary" },
      { "front": "außerhalb des Gebäudes", "back": "outdoor" },
      { "front": "äußerst schwierig", "back": "most difficult" },
      { "front": "äußerster", "back": "outermost" },
      { "front": "Äußerung", "back": "remark" },
      { "front": "ausfindig machen", "back": "come across" },
      { "front": "ausfüllen(Br.)", "back": "fill in" },
      { "front": "ausfüllen(US)", "back": "fill out" },
      { "front": "Ausgabe", "back": "issue" },
      { "front": "Ausgaben", "back": "expense" },
      { "front": "Ausgang", "back": "exit" },
      { "front": "ausgeben", "back": "spend (irr.)" },
      { "front": "ausgebreitet", "back": "spread" },
      { "front": "ausgegeben", "back": "spent" },
      { "front": "ausgehen", "back": "go out" },
      { "front": "ausgehend", "back": "outgoing" },
      { "front": "ausgeliehen", "back": "lent" },
      { "front": "ausgeschaltet", "back": "off" },
      { "front": "ausgezeichnet", "back": "excellent" },
      { "front": "aushöhlen", "back": "hollow out" },
      { "front": "auskommen mit", "back": "get along with" },
      { "front": "Auskunft", "back": "information" },
      { "front": "Ausländer", "back": "foreigner" },
      { "front": "ausländisch", "back": "foreign" },
      { "front": "Auslandspolitik", "back": "foreign politics" },
      { "front": "Auslaß", "back": "outlet" },
      { "front": "auslassen", "back": "omit" },
      { "front": "Ausmaß", "back": "extent" },
      { "front": "aufmerksam", "back": "attentive" },
      { "front": "Ausnahme", "back": "exception" },
      { "front": "auspacken", "back": "unpack" },
      { "front": "Ausruf", "back": "outcry" },
      { "front": "ausrutschen", "back": "slip" },
      { "front": "Ausrutscher", "back": "slip" },
      { "front": "ausschalten", "back": "turn off" },
      { "front": "Ausschau halten", "back": "look out" },
      { "front": "Ausschuss", "back": "committee" },
      { "front": "ausschweifend", "back": "gay" },
      { "front": "Aussehen", "back": "looks" },
      { "front": "Aussichtspunkt", "back": "look-out" },
      { "front": "Aussprache", "back": "pronunciation" },
      { "front": "aussprechen", "back": "pronounce" },
      { "front": "ausstehend", "back": "outstanding" },
      { "front": "ausstellen", "back": "exhibit" },
      { "front": "Aussteller", "back": "exhibitor" },
      { "front": "Ausstellung", "back": "exhibition" },
      { "front": "Ausstoß", "back": "output" },
      { "front": "Austausch", "back": "exchange" },
      { "front": "Austausch von Gefangenen", "back": "exchange of prisoners" },
      { "front": "austauschen", "back": "exchange" },
      { "front": "austeilen", "back": "deal" },
      { "front": "Australien", "back": "Australia" },
      { "front": "ausverkaufen", "back": "sell out" },
      { "front": "Auswahl", "back": "choice" },
      { "front": "ausweiten", "back": "widen" },
      { "front": "auswendig", "back": "by heart" },
      { "front": "ausziehen (Kleid)", "back": "take off" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "V Dictionary Deck 1",
    "slug": "dictionary-deck-2",
    "tags": ["#german"],
    "cards": [
      { "front": "verwelkte Blumen", "back": "faded flowers" },
      { "front": "verwirklichen", "back": "realize" },
      { "front": "verwirren", "back": "puzzle" },
      { "front": "verwöhnen", "back": "spoil (irr.)" },
      { "front": "verwöhnt", "back": "spoilt" },
      { "front": "verwöhnte", "back": "spoilt" },
      { "front": "verwunden", "back": "wound" },
      { "front": "Verwunderung", "back": "wonder" },
      { "front": "verwundet", "back": "wounded" },
      { "front": "verwurzelt", "back": "rooted" },
      { "front": "Verzeichnis", "back": "register" },
      { "front": "verzeihen", "back": "pardon" },
      { "front": "Verzeihung", "back": "pardon" },
      { "front": "verzichten auf", "back": "do without" },
      { "front": "verzieh", "back": "forgave" },
      { "front": "verziehen", "back": "forgiven" },
      { "front": "verzieren", "back": "ornament" },
      { "front": "Verzierung", "back": "ornament" },
      { "front": "verzögern", "back": "delay" },
      { "front": "Verzögerung", "back": "delay" },
      { "front": "verzweifeln", "back": "despair" },
      { "front": "verzweifelt", "back": "desperate" },
      { "front": "Verzweiflung", "back": "despair" },
      { "front": "verzweigen", "back": "branch" },
      { "front": "Vetter", "back": "cousin" },
      { "front": "Vieh treiben", "back": "drive (irr.)" },
      { "front": "viel", "back": "much" },
      { "front": "viel Geld", "back": "plenty of money" },
      { "front": "Viel Glück !", "back": "good luck !" },
      { "front": "viel größer", "back": "much bigger" },
      { "front": "viel mehr", "back": "much more" },
      { "front": "Viel Vergnügen !", "back": "have a good time !" },
      { "front": "viel zu essen", "back": "plenty of food" },
      { "front": "viele", "back": "many" },
      { "front": "viele Leute", "back": "many people" },
      { "front": "vielen Dank !", "back": "thank you very much !" },
      { "front": "vielleicht", "back": "perhaps" },
      { "front": "vier", "back": "four" },
      { "front": "vierte", "back": "fourth" },
      { "front": "Viertel", "back": "quarter" },
      { "front": "Viertel nach", "back": "a quarter past" },
      { "front": "Viertel vor", "back": "a quarter to" },
      { "front": "vierteljährlich", "back": "quarterly" },
      { "front": "Viertelstunde", "back": "quarter" },
      { "front": "vierzehn", "back": "fourteen" },
      { "front": "vierzehn Tage", "back": "fortnight" },
      { "front": "vierzehnte", "back": "fourteenth" },
      { "front": "vierzig", "back": "forty" },
      { "front": "vierzigste", "back": "fortieth" },
      { "front": "Violine", "back": "violin" },
      { "front": "Vogel", "back": "bird" },
      { "front": "Vogelfeder", "back": "feather" },
      { "front": "Volk", "back": "people" },
      { "front": "volkommen machen", "back": "perfect" },
      { "front": "Volksstamm", "back": "tribe" },
      { "front": "voll", "back": "full" },
      { "front": "voll Respekt", "back": "respectful" },
      { "front": "voll Sorge", "back": "sorrowful" },
      { "front": "völlig", "back": "entire" },
      { "front": "vollkommen", "back": "perfect" },
      { "front": "vollkommenes Glück", "back": "entire happiness" },
      { "front": "Vollkommenheit", "back": "perfection" },
      { "front": "vollständig", "back": "complete" },
      { "front": "Volumen", "back": "volume" },
      { "front": "vom Boden aufheben", "back": "pick up" },
      { "front": "vom Geschäft reden", "back": "talk business" },
      { "front": "von", "back": "of" },
      { "front": "von (... her)", "back": "from" },
      { "front": "von ... bis", "back": "from ... to" },
      { "front": "von einem Konto abheben", "back": "draw from an account" },
      { "front": "von etwas abhängen", "back": "depend on something" },
      { "front": "von etwas reden", "back": "talk about something" },
      { "front": "von fester Beschaffenheit", "back": "solid" },
      { "front": "von Geburt an", "back": "by birth" },
      { "front": "von oben bis unten", "back": "from top to bottom" },
      { "front": "von Shakespeare", "back": "by Shakespeare" },
      { "front": "von Würmern gefressen", "back": "worm-eaten" },
      { "front": "voneinander abhängig", "back": "interdependent" },
      { "front": "vor", "back": "before" },
      { "front": "vor 1980", "back": "before 1980" },
      { "front": "vor allem", "back": "most of all" },
      { "front": "vor dem Gebäude", "back": "in front of the building" },
      { "front": "vor kurzem", "back": "recently" },
      { "front": "vor langer Zeit", "back": "a long time ago" },
      { "front": "vor zwei Tage", "back": "two days ago" },
      { "front": "voran gehen", "back": "go ahead" },
      { "front": "voraus", "back": "ahead" },
      { "front": "vorbei an", "back": "by" },
      { "front": "vorbeifahren", "back": "pass by" },
      { "front": "vorbeigehen", "back": "pass" },
      { "front": "vorbereiten", "back": "prepare" },
      { "front": "Vorbereitung", "back": "preparation" },
      { "front": "Vorbild", "back": "model" },
      { "front": "Vorderside", "back": "front" }
    ]
  }
]
